Hi. My name is Patrick Debois, and I'm the content curator of AI DevCon, a conference
dedicated to software engineering with AI. The central theme is
software factories and everything around it, from context to prompting to
harness. We'll have workshops, we'll have keynotes, and new for this year,
the enterprise track. It's going to be really, really a learning experience
of people sharing their knowledge from the industry to their peers.
That's why I'm very pleased to announce our enterprise track.
People willing to share their stories on doing things at scale.
These are talks from the trenches in larger organizations, and they're rare
to find. We'll have folks from Booking talking about their platform.
We'll have folks from Amazon talking about their experiences internally
and guide them. Customers, people from Mistral helping people adapt when
new models are released. The workshops at AI DevCon are hands-on and
practical. You'll learn things by doing, and the full three-day ticket gets
you access to the workshops as well as all the talks on days two and three.
Speaking of which. AI has brought us this firehose of new ideas, and I
love it when people share their experiences.
I personally even love it more when there are people on the trenches.
Very much on the edge of the new technology.
That's why I'm really glad to have Ryan Lopopolo from Google Cloud to help
us explain more on harness engineering, a term that he himself coined.
We also Geoffrey Huntley, kind of came up with the idea of a Ralph loop.
The goal-seeking for the agent.
Really powerful in your toolkit.
And last but not least, like, Steve, kind of the vendor of Gas Town, the inspirer
of so many people kind of doing things on the edge and exploring the whole
new world, AI and agentic coding.
With the help of our sponsors, we made it really easy and accessible for
you to attend the... If you want to have some extra off, just use YT15
to get even a 15%... Nothing really beats an in-person event, right?
But maybe, you know, you can't... Like.
So why don't you join our livestream?
You'll see the keynotes. You'll see what's happening at the event and after
the event. You can also watch the videos online on our YouTube... What makes
me think is learning, and there's no more pleasure than to share that
learning with others. That's why we have this event, and I hope you come
to learn as well and share your story in New York.